I am saying this for myself as well as
for anyone it speaks to my job is not to
convince the world the masses that what
I say is true my job is to speak my
truth and find people who resonate with
it
and to my truth what I see is the truth
is that every single human being on this
planet is worthy exactly as they are
they are exactly who they are supposed
to be to spark to start to hinder to
help to do everything they're here to do
for what I want to call the coming
revolution which isn't coming it's here
we're already living it but the more
people who wake up to their authenticity
and to their perfection in them being
themselves them encompassing their
talents their challenges their life
experiences and bringing that to the
table the faster we can create the
infrastructure that helps us easily find
our people easily fine or more easily
find our genius and our gifts and have
help with each other in our challenges a
lot of what we're doing right now on
this planet is reacting to other people
who aren't following our life path and
it's highly triggering us because we're
not following our own you cannot judge
anybody else because they're following
their own map even if they're not the
universe God the essence that of magic
that I have no idea how to explain the
science but it keeps proving itself
beyond coincidence all you have to have
is curiosity and step forward and it
will prove itself to you time and time
and time again there's no other religion
or belief system that I see on this
planet
it does that besides maybe science but
even that has become this is like the
realm outside of science probe outside
of what can be proven collectively
through scientific method there was a
path that each of us is meant to follow
a GPS system that you can only read
internally so nobody else can read it
for you no one else can give you your
map and when you start following your
map you find your people you find your
purpose you get a sense of being and
completeness and happiness and as you
get that it proves itself to you there
is nothing external that you need
including along the path now of course
there's external stuff you need but that
just falls away incrementally as you
follow your path you find the people and
you start to see that everybody is
worthy everybody is on their own journey
and we're here to assist one another not
to judge one another but if what you're
capable of in the moment is judging one
another judging other people that's
exactly where you're supposed to be
there is an unfolding to this process
and fold into humanity in ourselves and
right now we're in a very chaotic time
we don't want to wake up to our power we
don't want to wake up to our individual
genius we want to leave it to the other
there is a handful of us that are ready
ready to wake up because it is
incremental and you keep getting power
and you keep getting genius and you keep
getting more authenticity and you start
seeing it in other people and so a tiny
fraction of us doing that starts to
unleash all of humanity when we create a
tiny bit of the collaboration
infrastructure to assist everyone in
that path everyone to find their people
no matter where they are even if they
can't see humanity every one in humanity
is worthy we are different cells of the
body we are different species of
Ecosystem humans in all of our beautiful
diversity is exactly what this world
needs I can see it and I'm okay but it
triggers some people because that's
exactly what is supposed to happen
the right people will find us the right
people will come see the beauty the gift
in what we are gonna offer each other
and help create a world that works for
everyone
a better world is on its way we all get
to help in creating it we already are
all you have to do is be you you have
enough knowledge you have enough
compassion you have enough connections
and the ones you need along the journey
will show up if you just step forward
thank you